Why are you doing this for me?
I want you to go back to your landing castle, so you can find out where the real Princess of Salem is being held.
But why would you trust me?
Because I believe you want the same thing Princess of Salem does.
There's one other thing I want you to find out for me.
Slain Troyart's objective. What's his plan?
His objective?
Take this.
When you meet with the real Princess of Salem, give this to her.
She'll know you're among those on her side.
Oh, my lady!
To be continued...
Thank you.
Well done.
By combining Alt-Noah's power with Earth's resources, we will begin to build our world.
Thank you.
Maybe Command thinks the odds are somehow on their side.
So then do you think those odds will extend to us as well?
I don't, ma'am.
In that case, we may want to do some calculating of our own.
Well, some input would be nice.
Young Kaiska, that brain of yours got anything we can use against those Martians?
It's really tricky.
Electris uses lightning as a weapon.
Scandia turns invisible.
Both are formidable.
As far as the Ortegia's duplicating ability, I'll need to get more data.
Lightning, invisible, and the cloner.
It's like we're stuck in a superhero film.
We know from our experience that when the Ortegia reproduces, it always splits from one into two.
It never multiplies into three or more.
And the new clone always appears within a radius of 30 meters.
No matter how many times it splits, there's got to be only one living pilot, right?
The rest are drones.
So then we've got to identify and destroy the original.
But how are we going to do that?
We put some kind of mark on the original and keep track of it after that.
And as for the other ones, we know we can use smoke to track Scandia's movements.
And the lightning one?
Any ideas there?
We get hit by that one, it'll blow out our electronics and our control systems again.
Well, what about some insulation?
That doesn't conduct electricity.
Huh?
Any brains in that head?
What are you, a grade schooler?
What do you mean?
And what is so wrong with that idea?
Air is already a very good insulator.
There's no way to block a discharge powerful enough to punch through so much insulation.
I'll tell you what makes it really tricky.
The fact that they've been teaming up instead of competing against each other.
Yeah, they're bad enough just one at a time.
Now wait a minute.
I have an idea.
Your eye.
You're not going to use it now, are you?
There's nothing to worry about, Inko.
It's alright.
Huh?
I always have a self-mutating code running, so it gets more and more optimized over time.
Its predictive ability is even more accurate now.
Com, can you manage a loadout change for me?
No problem.
Just tell me what you need.
What I had in the space fight.
I need those.
Princess Lamrina, I thought you'd like to know.
The Earth invasion is well in hand.
I see.
I knew you could do it, Slane.
And perhaps, for morale, could you say a few words to the Orbital Knights who served so well in battle?
You mean that I should speak to them?
Yes, if Princess Asalem were to honor their achievements, more knights could be won over to our side.
To our side?
Yes, Princess Lamrina.
Very well, then.
Incidentally, Slane, what is my sister's current medical status?
Unfortunately, the reports say she is still in critical condition.
I see.
For now, all we can do is maintain our faith in the medical staff.
That is true.
Of course, we shall pray for a quick recovery.
Try not to dwell on it, Slane.
I thank you, Your Highness.
You're very kind.
Now, please excuse me.
You are a liar.
This is Clydesdale leader to all units.
Spread out and maintain distance.
Mustang leader to Mustang Zero-Zero.
Now, what's their position?
Preliminary data is in.
Sending coordinates and velocity.
Mustang 1-1 and 2-2.
Go, move out!
Roger!
Primary target is the Ortegium Master.
Let's get him boxed up.
Take him down, now.
Saria platoon, straight ahead.
Gauntlet platoon, flank him from the west.
Saria platoon, acknowledged.
Gauntlet platoon, acknowledged.
Master identified on the right.
Third from the end.
Commence attack!
Did you really think you had the original?
Well, guess again.
Aye, Count Olga will deal with this enemy force.
Nonius platoon, Plevin platoon.
Concentrate attack on the Scandia.
Let's take him out.
Fire smoke grenades!
Spotted him!
On my nine!
Fire! Fire! Fire!
Using the same old tricks again.
You are very tedious, aren't you?
What do you think we should do with them?
Ideas, Count Zebrin?
Let us show them a little magic.
Shall we, Countess Raffia?
The smoke screen just vanished.
Smoke is a colloid, and ionization settles it out.
But here is another way to use.
The power of lightning.
Lightning attack from invisibility?
When one is defeated in a battle,
shouldn't it be a beautiful death?
Assuming you are a true cataphract pilot.
Captain!
Both the main force and our assault units are running into trouble!
That's what I was afraid of.
Invisible and Lightning are now a team.
Mustang Zero Zero, what's your status?
I've got the data.
Smoke screen negation and expanded invisibility field were unexpected, though.
Can you make an adjustment?
I have to.
So then, this war has been going on for almost two years now, while I was unconscious?
Yes.
And it is slain?
Who...
What has been going on?
I don't understand.
Milady!
Where are you going?
I'm going to see slain.
To learn the truth behind all this.
But, Milady!
Wait, who are...
Tell me why.
Why must you always stand in my way?
But who are you?
Who am I?
I am you, of course.
Using a tactical data link for multidimensional analysis of enemy behavior to deduce the enemy's battle habits,
We will deploy friendlies in positions vulnerable to the enemy's preferred attack patterns,
then prompt them to engage.
But will the analysis be complete in time?
Sending most recent data.
Take your positions.
Roger.
Roger from over here, too.
The probability is he's right-handed.
He moves counterclockwise to attack enemies on his left.
I don't care much for being bait.
Where is he now?
He's circling around behind you.
To keep from giving away his position, he'll hold off on his lightning attack.
Then, once behind his target, he'll come to a quick stop and take aim.
Yuki, now!
Is he really there?
Found him!
What was that?
This is Mustang Leader.
We have the target spotted.
Mustang Zero-Zero, launching.
Roger that.
Mustang Zero-Zero, go drop!
This Scandia's leg.
It can't support the extra weight of Electris.
Disconnect the link.
I will handle it.
Get clear.
Targets confirmed.
Firing anchors.
You know that will not work.
And what about these rounds?
How can you...
Lightning flows from high potential to low.
It won't strike an object with the same electrical potential.
That's what keeps you from striking yourself.
Take this!
It's too late.
The cables gave us the same potential.
Come stop you now.
It cannot be.
Is this that orange one I've heard about?
Count Zebrin, no!
I'm sending you help.
Just hold on.
No, Inoho!
Smoke grenades!
There you are.
Fire!
Curse you.
You murdered my noble comrades.
I will avenge them.
Now, are you okay?
Yes, thanks, Yuki.
On your nine!
Cause it's time to wake you up.
Here they come!
Fire and will!
You wish to see me, Princess Lemrina?
Yes, Slane.
What do you think you're up to?
About Princess Asalem. My sister. She has actually awakened, hasn't she?
I knew that I would have to tell you eventually.
I think it's time you explained yourself.
Unfortunately, Princess Asalem is not quite herself yet.
I need you to portray her still, just for the time being, until her health improves and she has had a chance to recover, in order for us to create a new world.
To create a new world?
Yes. A world that is free of worry. A world of everlasting peace, that is without conflict and without sadness.
And who do you have in mind to rule this world?
Her Highness. Asalem vs. Alucia, of course.
Do you think that she even wants such a thing?
I know for a fact she does not. Which is the reason why it has to be presented to her.
Your Highness, do you know why it is that wars break out?
Wars are a means of negotiation between states.
Not quite. Wars always break out because there is someone there to fight against.
There are two options to eliminate war. Invade and assimilate, or exterminate your adversary so that only you remain.
The history of mankind is the history of conflict.
At the very instant Mars split off from Earth, war became an utter inevitability.
It's true. If I had not started this war, eventually, someone else would have.
You're not the same. Something has changed in you.
No. You are no longer the gentle slain I once knew, are you?
No. Princess Asalem.
I told her everything.
In the name of the Verse Empire, Asalem vs. Alucia, Royal Princess.
Hereby orders Count Slain Sosbaum Troyard to immediately cease hostilities.
I thought getting the Master would bring this to an end.
But which is the real one?
Obviously, the one we marked wasn't the original.
Where's that bastard hiding?
I assumed that one of these guys would be the original, but it may actually be incorrect.
Inaho, what do you mean?
In analyzing the duplicates, I learned something interesting.
At the instant they manifest, the Master's state is perfectly duplicated, from orientation to energy level.
And that means what?
I believe he's using quantum teleportation to manufacture these copies.
Except the original is left intact instead of being destroyed, creating a perfect duplicate.
Again? What the hell does that mean?
What it means is...
Hmm.
That they are all the real one.
Slave all of the cataphract platoons into my fire controls.
Send request to company command post.
Yes, ma'am.
Locating all Ortegeus.
Their vectors and coordinates.
How many more is he gonna make?
Right now would be good, young Kaizuka.
Target numbers increasing.
I need to update my data.
Do what you gotta do, but quick!
Our ammo isn't gonna last forever!
Tactical data linking completed.
Slave all UFV cataphract aiming systems to my control.
Now, how much longer?
We have one chance.
If they're all real...
All targets now locked.
Fire!
Oh, wow.
Every one of them was real, so they all had to be taken care of at once.
Enemy cataphracts totally eliminated!
Wow, you did it, Inahal!
Mm-hmm.
I'm just glad that it worked.
Thanks for all your help.
Slain.
Please, you have to end this madness.
Princess Asalem.
I'm afraid I cannot obey your order.
For you see,
I am no longer a citizen of the Verse Empire.
I'm truly sorry.
But I must take you all into custody.
Captain, a message from General Headquarters.
Sorry, you'll only have about two minutes before the comm satellite dips below the line of sight, ma'am.
I hope that'll be enough.
Put it on speaker, if you would.
Deucalion here.
Captain Mogberech speaking.
This is Vice Admiral Aelis Hokinen.
That was a brilliant operation, Captain.
What is your status on the upgrades?
Almost finished, sir.
I am very pleased to hear it.
The Deucalion will need this equipment on her next mission.
Will we be going to the satellite belt?
Is that it?
No.
It'll be higher this time.
You will be breathed later.
Connection is broken.
The laser link gain is starting to fade.
Comm satellite now leaving line of sight.
I guess he didn't want to hear me say no.
Sounds like we could be in for a large battle.
Damn it all.
He thinks he can put us into play any way he wants, because we have Alt-Noah.
So then it's a space loadout, ma'am?
A catapult module, too.
My Lord Slane.
What is it?
The princesses are comfortably settled in their quarters.
Thank you.
My Lord, you had to do this.
Even if they don't understand now, one day they...
No matter.
Whether they understand or not is irrelevant.
My Lord Count, a spaceship is on approach to the base.
They request permission to dock.
Who is on this ship?
A visitor from the Verse Homeworld.
So that is the planet Earth.
The bounteous blue world where my father is interred.
Yes, Count Cruteo, it is.
Oh, please don't do that.
I find it a bit awkward when I'm addressed by my father's name.
Please, call me Clonkane.
As you would prefer.
My Lord, Clonkane, then.
Thank you.
I can't help but wonder what he will be like.
Let's go meet the son of Dr. Troyard.
We are on this ship.
z
of
in
i
I can't believe it's impossible
The叫び is still far away
But I can't believe it's going to be flying
Even if it's not forever
Even if it's not perfect
You can't believe it's impossible
I can't believe it's impossible
If it's not perfect
As you can't believe it's impossible
delay